A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Art, Series C FA340
Rockefeller Archive Center
- CKU Reference Files, 1949-1979; 3; 27.6 Cubic Feet
  - Barr-Miller/NAR Art (M-P), 1950-1968 (Box 9, Folder 62)
    MacEntyre Maillol Marcarelli Marisol Marquet Martins, Aldemir Maselli Mastroianni Mathieu Matisse Meredith, John Mir Minguzzi Modigliani Mondrian Moore Motherwell Munter, Jawlensky Negret Noland Obregn Orion Pan Paolozzi Peto
  - Barr-Miller/NAR Art (Picasso), 1950-1968 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Barr-Miller/NAR Art (Picasso), 1950-1968 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Barr-Miller/NAR Art (Picasso), 1950-1968 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Barr-Miller/NAR Art (P-R), 1950-1968 (Box 10, Folder 66)
    Polesello, Rogelio Pollock Pomodoro Prints Reder Reinhoud Revern Rivera, Manuel Rodins Rosai Rouault
  - Barr-Miller/NAR Art (S), 1950-1968 (Box 10, Folder 67)
    Sani Schoffer Scipion Sculpture Smith, David Silrano, Lora Snelson Somaini Soulages Stahly Stankiewicz Stefanelli Stella Sugarman
  - Barr-Miller/NAR Art (T-W), 1950-1968 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    Tajiri Takis Tanguy Tomlin Trova Uecker Valtat van Dongen Vickrey Vivancos Vlaminck Weiss Wotruba
  - Barr-Miller/NAR Art - NAR Miscellaneous, 1950-1968 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Barr-Miller/NAR Art - David Rockefeller/John D. Rockefeller 3rd (CLOSED FOLDER), 1950-1968 (Box 10, Folder 70)
    Bonnard Camoigli Gris Gauguin/van Gogh Moore Miro/Picasso Monet Picasso
  - Belgian Congo, Royal Museum of, 1935-1955, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 71)
    Correspondence re NAR purchases and gifts from the museum. Catalogs and postcards.
  - Belgian Congo, Royal Museum of, 1935-1955, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Books, 1950-1954 (Box 10, Folder 73)
    Correspondence, memoranda and invoices re the purchase, storage and location of books about NAR's collection or Modern Art.
  - Books, 1958-1960 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Books, 1961-1969 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Books, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - Books, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Books, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Books, 1976-1978 (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - Brooklyn Museum, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 80)
    Correspondence, memoranda, photographs and publicity for an exhibit of NAR art.
  - Cabell - Campos (Box 11, Folder 81)
    Cabell, Dr. Margaret Cabral, Mary N. Caccia, David A. Cadby-Birch Gallery Cain, J. L. Calabrese, Mrs. Salvatore Calder, Alexander Caldwell, Ben Caldwell, Susan Caldonie Calhoun, H. S. California State University, Fresno Callery, Mary Callinan, J. J. Calliyannis, Manolis Calman, Michel Calocerinos, Joanne Cambell, Rodney Cambodian Sculpture Cameron, H. H. Camillwei, Louis Campana, Paul Jr. Campbell, Elsie Campbell, Kenneth Campbell, Robert Campbell, Robin Campbell, Mrs. Roy N. Campos, Florencia Molina
  - Canadian - Cappellini (Box 11, Folder 82)
    Canadian Cancer Society Canadian Conservation Institute Cancer Care Cannamela, A. Canzeri, Joe W. Capa, Cornell Cape Dorset Caple, Shirley M. Capon, Edmund Caponnetto, Joseph Capelletti, Father E. J. Cappello, C. Cappellini, Luigi
  - Caravanos - Carey (Box 11, Folder 83)
    Caravanos, Emanuel Carewe, Sylvia Carey, Mrs. Charles J. Carey, Mrs. M. J.
  - Carlin - Casson (Box 11, Folder 84)
    Carlin, Virginia dePaulis Carnegie Institute Carnegie Study of the Arts of the United States Carneiro Netto, Vincente Carpenter Center for the Visual Arts Carpousis, Henry A. Carr, Louis Carroll, John M. Carroll, Margaret R. Cartier, Ferdinand P. Sr. Carton, Norman Cascella, Two Worlds Casey, Albert V. Cash, R. H. Caso, Ralph Cassidy, Appolonia H. Casson, Iris
  - Castano Galleries - CBS (Box 11, Folder 85)
    Castano Galleries Castano, Giovanni Castelli Gallery Castille, Patrick Castle, June Castleman, Riva Castrovillo, Elna Catharine Lorillard Wolfe Art Club, Inc. Catherwood prints Cats Catskilll Art Exhibition Catto, Mrs. Henry (Jessica) Cavasin, John Caylor, George N. Cazenave, Andre CBS
  - Cebbar - Cerveira (Box 11, Folder 86)
    Cebbar, Zeytune Cenedella, Robert Center for Inter-American Relations Center for the Fine Arts Centre Georges Pompidon Centre for the Study of Modern Art Century Club Cerveira, Adele Chelz, Cheryl
  - Chadwick - Chavez (Box 12, Folder 87)
    Chadwick, Lynn Chagall, Marc Chait, Ralph Chakrian, Hagop Challenor, Mary Chamberlain, G. L. Chamblet, M. Gaston Champion, Tom Chandler, Jean E. Chanin, Arnold Chanin, Margit W. Channel 13 Channel 17 Channel 21 Channel 24 Channel 46 Chapellier Gallery Chapman, Herman H. Chapman, Ita Chapman, Liane W-T Chapman, Mrs. Walter (Jean) Chapman, Walter Chase, Michael F. Chautauqua Art Association Chavez, Joseph A.
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Railroad - Chrino (Box 12, Folder 88)
    Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company Chencinski, Erna Cherina Cheesman, Paul Cheung, Michael Chiara, Enzo de Chicago Museum of Contemporary Art Children's Art Gallery Chinese Art Set Chinese Ceramics Chinese Pottery Chinese, Sung Vase Ching, Peter S. Chinni, Peter Chirino, Martin
  - Chitwood - Chuong (Box 12, Folder 89)
    Chlewbowski, Wojciech Chong, Chunteck Chow, Fong Chriqui, Yann Christie's Catalogue Orders Christie, Mason and Woods, Ltd. Christo Christy, Howard Chandler Chryssa Chuong, Pham Mong
  - Ciarlo - Cleren (Box 12, Folder 90)
    Ciarlo, Franco Ciccodicola, Rafael Cisneros, Florencia Garcia Civale, Biagio Civic Fine Arts Association Clark, Joseph W. Clark, Patrick Clarke, Mrs. Edmund C. Clarke, Gregory V. Clarke, John L. Clarkson, Ursilla R. Clausen, Mrs. Harold Cleaver, F. E. Clert, Iris Cleveland Museum of Art Cloisonn Screen Cleren, Jean-Paul
  - Coates - Comstock (Box 12, Folder 91)
    Coates, Josephine Coates, Mary Coburn, John Cochran, Harry Leroy Cockburn, Olive E. Cockerr Gallery Coffy, Pauline Cohen, Phyllis M. Colby College Cole, Mignon Cole, Nancy Otis Cole, Sylvan Coleman, A. B. Coles, Mignon Colli, Sam Colin, Ralph Collection, January 1974 list of colleges and universities where NAR lent group show Collection Inventory "Collector in America" Collector's Directory College Art Association of America Collens, David R. Collie, Alberto Collier, Dr. Donald Collinson, Mrs. Gordon Colonial Mint, The Columbia University Columbus Gallery of Fine Arts Columbus, Joseph Colville, Alex Combemalle, Collette Complete Placement Training of Kerygma Computer Records Computerization Comstock, John Albert
  - Concepcion - Cordry (Box 12, Folder 92)
    Concepcion, Isis Condon, Rudolph E. Cordry, Donald
  - Cone - Conservation/Restoration (Box 12, Folder 93)
    Cone, Fred Cornell Congolese Paintings Conkright, Rachel "Connaissance des Arts" Connely, Willard Connelly, Robert Conrad, Tony Constantine, Mildred Contemporaries, The Contemporary Arts Association of Houston Contemporary Arts Center of Cincinnati, Ohio Contemporary Arts Exhibition, Dallas Contemporary Arts Museum (Houston, Texas) Contemporary Christian Art, Inc. Conroueia, George Conservation./Restoration Paper Conservation: Art Conservation Associates, Inc. Conservation/Restoration
  - Cook - Coover (Box 13, Folder 94)
    Cook, J. R. Cook, Marion Beldon Cooley, Mrs. H. M. Cooper, Charles Cooper, Ella M. Cooper, Mary Cooper Hewitt Museum of Decorative Arts Cooper, Nathan N. Cooper, Robert S. Cooperman, Norma Bezrod Cooperstown Coover, Dede
  - Copains - Corrigan (Box 13, Folder 95)
    Copains Association Copeland, L. H. Copeland, Elliot L. Coppock, Jack Corbin, Sol and Tanya Corcoran Gallery of Art Corn, Freda Cornell University Cornely, Josef Corning Glass Center Correll, Allen Corrigan, Robert
  - Cosmic - Coste (Box 13, Folder 96)
    Cosmic Theater Restaurant Cosmopolitan Club Cosson, Dina Costanini, Egidio Costantino, D'Argenio Costanzo, Elsa H. Costanzo, Joseph
  - Cosmic - Coste (Box 13, Folder 0096A)
    Coste, Ann Rockefeller
  - Coughlin - Coxe (Box 13, Folder 97)
    Coughlin, Marion Coulter, Elizabeth Council on Foundations Country Floors Courtwright, Mrs. Hernando Courtais, Henri Coveney, Mrs. Richard J. Coviello, Peter Covin, M. Covino, Isaac Cowan, Carolyn Horton Cowart, Jack Cowles, Charles Cox, Sally Cox, Warren E. Coxe, Mrs. Henry B. Jr.
  - Cracker Barrel Club - Cruickshank (Box 13, Folder 98)
    Cracker Barrel Club Craig, Richard E. Craig, Ralph C. Crain, Lloyd Cramer, H. M. Cramer, Robert S. Crampton, Rollin Cranmer, Dana Crawford, Jane Crawford, Margaret Crmartie, Jim Crompton, Robert D. Croquis Gallery Crosson, Mrs. Joe Croteau, J. O. Crotti, M. Crouch, Donald E. Crowson, Enoch E. Cruickshank, Ward
  - Cracker Barrel Club - Cruickshank (Box 13, Folder 0098A)
  - Cudroff - Cyril (Box 13, Folder 99)
    Cudroff, Louis Cueras, Jose Luis Robert B. Mayer, Son-in-law of Nathan Cummings Cummings, Paul Cunningham, Janice Cunningham, John J. Cunningham, Patty Curran, Anne E. Currie, Kit Currier Gallery of Art Currier & Ives Reproductions Cushman, Aaron D. & Associates, Inc. Cushman, Mrs. Arthur A. Customs Customs Brokers Cutting, George C. W. Post Center Art Gallery Cyril
  - Carlebach Gallery, 1949-1956 (Box 13, Folder 100)
    Correspondence re exhibitions of NAR art.
  - Carlebach Gallery, 1957-1958 (Box 13, Folder 101)
  - Cataloguing, 1950-1970 (Box 14, Folder 102)
    Lists of art experts, methods and procedures for cataloguing the NAR art collection.
  - Cataloguing, 1950-1970 (Box 14, Folder 103)
  - Chi-Yuan, Wang, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 104)
    Offer to loan/sell Chinese art works to New York State.
  - Christmas Cards, 1972-1978 (Box 14, Folder 105)
    Memoranda, proofs, and samples of NAR and Mrs. Rockefeller's Christmas cards.
  - Christmas Gifts, 1951-1975 (Box 14, Folder 106)
    Lists of art selections chosen to be given as gifts. Invoices for framing and restoration work.
  - Christmas Gifts, 1951-1975 (Box 14, Folder 0106A)
  - Christmas Gifts, 1951-1975 (Box 14, Folder 107)
  - Christmas Gifts, 1951-1975 (Box 14, Folder 0107A)
  - Colby College, 1959-1961 (Box 14, Folder 108)
    Correspondence and memoranda re loan of Seal Harbor pieces for an exhibit. Two catalogs from previous exhibits.
  - Colby College, 1959-1961 (Box 14, Folder 109)
  - Dabbs - D'Arcy Galleries (Box 15, Folder 110)
    Dabbs, Charles H. d'Adesky, R. G. Daedal Galleries Dagget, Noel J. D'Agostino, Mrs. T. Dahlin, Bengt Dahlquist, Mrs. E. S. Dalal, C. G. Dali, Salvador Dalkranian, Mihran K. Dallas Museum of Fine Art Dalsimek, Mrs. Samuel Daly, Mrs. Jack Dalzell Hatfield Galleries Damaz, Annie d'Amico, J. T. Damm, Robert L. Danaher, James T. Esq. Dannenberg, George Darby, James d'Arcangelo, Allan D'Arcy Galleries
  - Dash - Dawsons (Box 15, Folder 111)
    Dash, Harvey D. Datz, Harry J. Daughtery, Minnie da Veiga, Vinicio Davenport, Demorest Daves, Mrs. Delmar Davidson, Elizabeth Davidson, Irving Davies, Charles P. Davies, Kenneth Davis, Ben Davis, Mrs. I. Grady Davis, J. R. Davis, Roy Davis, Vachel Davison, Mrs. Waive S. Dawson's Book Shop
  - DCI International - de Kooning (Box 15, Folder 112)
    DCI International Dean, LaVenia de Aenlle Gallery De Bane, Gabriel J. Debany, Mrs. George De Bloe, Serge de Bournet, Francois de Bussigny, Jacqueline C. Decair Helicopters de Carvalho, Manuel A. Decelle, Paul H. Decelle, Mrs. Arthur de Creeft, Jos DeCrescenzo, Dominic T. De Domenico, Giuseppe Leonardo Defarias Mello Dehner, Dorothy de Herrara, Magda de Kooning
  - Delamare - Delvaux (Box 15, Folder 113)
    Delamare, Agents Maritime, Park de Laps, T. V. de la Rosa, Alberto Delbanco, Kurt Del Bello, Alfred B. Delgado Museum of Art Delgardo-Filardo, Pascua; & Jose de Lisio, Michael Dell, Robert Della Site, Mino Delp, George C. Delson, Theodore U. Delta College Delteil Delvaux, Paul
  - De Marco - Dey (Box 15, Folder 114)
    De Marco, Roland Dembeck, Richard De Mejo, Oscar De Meril, Christophe Demeulenaere, Mrs. D. Demmer, Vera Haberle Demmon, Isabel Demuth, Charles Denes, Agnes C. Denver Art Museum Detroit News Article on Mexican Art Derbes, Patricia B. Deree, Andre Derrick, Bob Derujinsky, Gleb W. De Sawal, Gertrude Desfor, Irving Detroit Institute of Arts - Founders Members Dey, Mukul Chandra
  - Diamond - Dlugosz (Box 15, Folder 115)
    Diamond, Elisa B. Dickinson College Dickstein, J. Dietrich, R. Krystyna DiFiore, Umberto di Giorgio, Patricia K. Dilowski, Wanda Dinchuk, Thomas Dintenfass Gallery Discovery Art Galleries Disla, Feliz Dittel, Miriam di Valentin, Louis Dlugosz, Louis
  - Dobbins - Doster (Box 15, Folder 116)
    Dobbins, Bill Dobkin, Blanche Dodge, William Dollarhide, Louis Domette, Elise Dominguez, Julian Dominion Gallery Dommers, Walter A. Donatus Donawa, Edward Leon Dongan, Mrs. Thomas Donish, J. Donnelly, Jack Jr. Donoso, Maria Perez de Dooley, J. Door Store Dormann, Henry O. Doster, Clifford H.
  - Douglass - Doyaga (Box 16, Folder 117)
    Douglas, Abe Douglas, Irene Douglas, Loretta Douglass, Robert Downes, Mrs. Olin Downing, Robert Downtown Gallery Doyaga, Emilia
  - Drake - Dryer (Box 16, Folder 118)
    Drake, Milton DRAGOS, Stephen Roberson Center for Arts and Sciences Drawing Society, The Drexler, Paul E. Dreyfus, Joan Personetto Driesbach, Janice T. Droney, Vincent R. Drori, Irene Droste, Karl-Heinz Drummond, Sally Hazelet Drummond, Venora Drydrynak, Bernard T. Dryer, Mr. and Mrs. Lee Roy
  - Drake - Dryer (Box 16, Folder 0118A)
  - DuBose - Dunne (Box 16, Folder 119)
    DuBose, Roy P Ducas, Patricia Dudensing, Leroy Dudensing, Valentine Duhl, Florence Dulles, Clover Dumenigo, Albert P. Duncan, Henry Duncan, Fred Duncan, Jack Dunigan, Phyllis R. Dunlap Society Dunn, Anne Dunn, Miss E. Myrtle Dunne, Emmaline
  - Dunningham - Dykes (Box 16, Folder 120)
    Dunningham, Margaret Duo Stat System Duridjoatmodjo, S. Durlacher Brothers Durrbach, Jacqueline de la Baume Durrbach, Rene Dutcher, Eleanor Dutchess County Art Association Dutton, E. P. Duty, G. G. Dwidjoatmadjo. S Dyer, Edith L. Dykes, John R.
  - Dartmouth College, 1955, 1962, 1969-1976 (Box 16, Folder 121)
    Correspondence re gifts and loans of NAR art.
  - Dartmouth College, 1955, 1962, 1969-1976 (Box 16, Folder 122)
  - Diamond, Harold, 1971-1978 (Box 16, Folder 123)
    Correspondence, memoranda and lists of NAR artworks sold through Harold Diamond.
  - Dubuffet, 1962-1968 (Box 16, Folder 124)
    Catalogs and photographs of Dubuffet works. Invoices and receipts for works purchases at Stuttgart auction.
  - Eagles - Edwards (Box 17, Folder 125)
    Eagle Eames Eanet, Phyllis Easby, Mrs. Dudley T. Jr. Eastman, Michael Eaton, Harriette Eberle, Hans Ebersole, Barbara Echavarry, Isabel M. Eckhardt, Tibor Edelich, Steven Editions de Larcos Editions le Moulin S A Edwards, Mrs. Orville D. Edwards, Sally Edwards, Sara
  - Eerkens - Ekholm (Box 17, Folder 126)
    Eerkens, Dr. and Mrs. J. W. Effinger, Frank W. Efrat, Benni Egan Gallery (Charles Egan) Egan, John Egyptian Urn Eiber, Rick Eidus, Alice Eikado East Eisele, David W. Eistrat, Sylvia Ekholm, Gordon F.
  - Elger - El Tiempo (Box 17, Folder 127)
    Elger, Marie E. Elkind, Eugene M. Elkins, Wayne Elkon, Robert Elliot-Smith, Cecily Ellsworth & Goldie, Ltd. Elmo, Mrs. J. Elmore, Ray E. Eloky, Thomas El Tiempo
  - Emeric - Emmerich (Box 17, Folder 128)
    Emeric Emig, A. Peter Emmerich, Andre (Andre Emmerich Gallery)
  - Encyclopaedia Judaica - Epstein (Box 17, Folder 129)
    Encyclopedia Judaica Engel, Martin Englert, E. English, Lisa Ennik, Gustave Enywart, E.P. Episcopal Mission Society Epner, David Epoxies Epstein, Irving Epstein, Jacob Epstein, Richard
  - Erana - Errett (Box 17, Folder 130)
    Erana, Jose Erdman, James P. Ergas, Milton Eriksen, Mrs. I. N. Erickson, H & R Erickson, Alex Erickson Collection Erlanger, M. Philippe Erlich, Irena Ernst, Max Errett, Raymond F.
  - Esbin - Eyre (Box 17, Folder 131)
    Esbin, Michael Eskimo Art Esman, Rosa Espejel, Carlos Esposito, Meade L'Estampe Originale Esterow, Milton Esteva, Calla Wheaton Estupinan, Cesar O. Araujo Eurich, Alice A. Evans, Alta M. Evans, Mrs. Clayton C. Evans, Governor Daniel J. Evans, E. Evans, Mark D. Exhibitions Experiments in Art and Technology Ewing, Kathleen M. H. Exxon Tapestry Eyre, Edward
  - Everson Museum, 1968-1975 (Box 17, Folder 132)
    Correspondence, memoranda, insurance information, condition reports, lists and publicity for loan for museum opening.
  - Everson Museum, 1968-1975 (Box 17, Folder 133)
  - Faibusch - Favro (Box 18, Folder 134)
    Faibusch, P. Faik-Duguet, Madame S. Fairbanks, A. Fairleigh Dickinson University Fanelli, Alfred Sr. Fang Shen Fans F.A.R. Gallery Farago, James Farhadi, Nuri Farian, Babette S. Faron, Clifton A. V. Farwell, Mrs. Maco Fasula, Muriel M. Fasulo, Carmen P. Fauvre, Christina Favro, Earle T. FDR Memorial Model
  - Fedder - Feuerlein (Box 18, Folder 135)
    Fedder, Felice Fedele, Frank Federal Deposit Insurance Corp. Federation of Jewish Philanthropies Feely, Leslie Fehrenbacher, Albert Feiden, Margo Feigen, Richard L. Feininger, Lyonel Feinsot, Louise Feinstein, Charles Feldgus, Robert Feller, Robert Feminist Art Journal, The Fennar, Charles Ferber, Herbert Ferdinand, Ida Ferdinand, Thomas Ferenczy, Zolta Ferguson, James Heston Ferguson, Richard Ferguson, Tana Y. Fergussonof, Donald C. Fernandez, Mrs. Fernandez, Manuel E. Fernando, J. M. Fernick, Bertha Ferrari, Mrs. Ilia Ferris, Margaret Ferris, Hugh Ferrugio, Reno Feuerlein, K. H.
  - Fidelman - Filsinger (Box 18, Folder 136)
    Fidelman, Paul H. Field Museum of Natural History Fields, Vivian Filardi, Del Filardi, Constantine Filinger, A. W. Filsinger & Company
  - Finch - Fioccardi (Box 18, Folder 137)
    Finch College Finch Gallery Findlay, David Findlay Gallery Fine Arts Association Fine Arts Conservation Laboratories, Inc. Fink, Clara Fink, Maurice Fink, Mrs. Nathan Finkelstein, Nancy Ellen Fioccardi, Teodoro
  - Finch - Fioccardi (Box 18, Folder 0137A)
  - Fischbach Gallery - Fisher (Box 18, Folder 138)
    Fischbach Gallery Fischer Fine Art Limited: London Fischer, Mrs. Leo Fishburne, St. Julian Fisher, Alan Fisher, Curtis M. Fisher, Geneva H. Fisher, Marie H. Fisher, Mary
  - Fitch - FMC Corporation (Box 18, Folder 139)
    Fitch, Lucille P. Fitler, William Crothers Flack, O. J. Flagging System, Tarrytown Flannery, Thomas V. Fledderus, Mary Fleishman, Myron Fleischner Maze Fleischner, Richard Fleiss, Marcel Fleming, Edward F. Fleschner, Cecelia R. Flint, Mr. & Mrs. Clarence A. Flint Institute Flood, Betty Flora Florentine Craftsmen Flores, Mercedes Floris, Beryl Flos, Charles R. Flowers, Betty FMC Corp.
  - Fodor - Forum Gallery (Box 18, Folder 140)
    Fodor, Franklin Fodor, Mrs. Nandor Fogg Art Museum Folk Art Fondation Maeght Fonelli, J. Vincent Force, Roland W. Fordham Art Club Fordham University Forest, Marie Forgotson, Windie Fort Worth Art Center Fortune Magazine Forum Antiquitarum Forum Gallery
  - Foundries - Fox (Box 18, Folder 141)
    Foundries Fourcade, Dominique Fourcade, Droll Inc. Fourcade, Xavier Fournier, Joseph Fox, Carl Fox Gallery Fox, Charles J. Fox, Mrs. Hammond R. Fox, William
  - Framing - Fusillo (Box 18, Folder 142)
    Framing Frackman, Mrs. Noel Frakes, Margaret Francis, Mrs. Edward T. Frank, Emily Frank, Harry Frank, Isabel S. Frank, Jane Frank, Jean Michael Frankel, Isador Frankel, Rochelle Frankenstein, Alfred V. Frankenthaler, Helen Frankfurter Kunstverein Franklin, John Jay Franks, Paul C. Fratelli Fabri Fredericka, Dolores Freedman, Mrs. Maurice (Louise A.) Freeman, Elois J. Freemont, Rita Freer Gallery Freiman, Robert Freitas de Andrade, Neuton French and Company Freshman, Robert S. Freund, Mary B. Friedman, Martin Friedman, Philip Friele, Berent Friends of the Corcoran Friuli Arts and Monuments Frost, David (David Frost Show) Frost, Terry Frumkin, Allan Fuchs, Luiz Fuhrmann, Mildred Furuta, Soichi Fusillo, Robert
  - FAVs-Fine Arts Valuation, 1966-1977 (Box 19, Folder 143)
    Correspondence with Gustave Gilbert of Fine Arts Valuation Service. Lists and memoranda re annual appraisals of NAR's collection.
  - FAVs-Fine Arts Valuation, 1966-1977 (Box 19, Folder 0143A)
  - FAVs-Fine Arts Valuation, 1966-1977 (Box 19, Folder 144)
  - Gaal - Gallwitz (Box 19, Folder 145)
    Gaal, Peter and Denes Gaal Gabriel, Jacques Gagarine, Mila Gagnon, Charles Eugene Gailis, Janis Gaitan, Fernando Gakken Co., Ltd. Galante, Michael Galeria Proteo Galeria Sudamericana Galerie Beyeler Galerie Christel Galerie Cramer Galerie Jean Bucher Galerie IM Griechenbeisl Galerie Louise Leiris Galerie Moderne Galerie Norval Gallagher, Thomas Gallander, Mrs. Thomas Gallaudet Galleria del Obelisco Galleria Odyssia Gallery Association of New York Gallery of Graphic Arts Gallotti Gallwitz, Klaus
  - Gangemi - Gayle (Box 19, Folder 146)
    Gangemi, Aida Gange, Aida Ganim, George Gannon, W. McK. Ganz, Mrs. Victor W. Garcia, Valentin Alonso Gardner, Esmond B. Garner, Keith Garofalides, George Garrard, Mary D. Garshanin, Katarina Garsson, Harriet Gasperini, George Gast, James E. Gast, Mrs. James E. Gault, Colonel Gavalas, Alexandros Beary Gayle, Marsha
  - Geglia - Gerson (Box 19, Folder 147)
    Geglia, Michael Gee, Helen (Yun Gee) Gee, Peter Geerts, Robert Geisinger, Marion Geller, Barry Geller, Linda Gelmond, Daniel Geluk, G. J. Genesis Galleries Gennari, F. & F. Gentils, Robert Gentry, Herbert George, Peter B. Gera, Bernice Thomas Gerard, Tony (Glacile Technique) Gerders, Wilhelm Gerety, Mrs. W. Gerken, Martin H. German Television Germanow, Mrs. Irving Germinal Otto Gerson Gallery Gerson, Otto
  - Getty - Ghosh (Box 19, Folder 148)
    Getty Museum Geyer, Betty Geyerhahn, Norberto Ghersi, Rosaria Ghosh, Borun
  - Giacometti - Gills (Box 19, Folder 149)
    Giacometti Lamps Gianamos, Stylianos Giannini, Rose Anne Gibford, Elaine Gibson, John Gibson, Sybil Gibson, Thomas Giffon, Mrs. Charles S. Gifford, Carl J. Giffords, Gloria Kay Gilbert, Gustave Gilbert, Regine Gilbon, Craig Gill, Bob Gill, Ray Gillespie, Beulah F. Gillespie, Dorothy Gillespie, Samuel H. III Gills, Phillip T.
  - Gilot - Gjermundsen (Box 20, Folder 150)
    Gilot, Francoise Gimpel Fils, Ltd. Gimpel Gallery Gimpel & WeitzenHoffer Ltd. Ginnever, Charles Ginsburg, Elizabeth Giobbi, Edward Gipson, Sally R. Girard, Alexander Gitler, Marco Giustozzi, Joseph Gjeneldon, Ella Howard Gjermundsen, Hildegard
  - Glasco - Gmurzynska (Box 20, Folder 151)
    Glasco, Joseph Glaser, Sioma Glas, Katherine Glass Glass Sculpture Glasser, Vera Glazer, Mary Todd Glenn, Hazel Glicksman, Abraham Glidden, Germain Glimcher, Arnold Glimcher, Mrs. Arnold Globus, F. Gluckmann - Coleman Inc. Glynn, Cliff Gmurzynska, Antonina
  - Goalwin - Goldmark (Box 20, Folder 152)
    Goalwin, Eva R. Gobuzas, Mrs. Aldona Goddard Neighborhood Center Goecke, Christine Goell, Abby Goenczoel, Janos Goldberg, Gary Goldberg, Ruth D. Goldberg, Verna M. Goldfield, Alfred Goldman, Louis Goldmark, Margo Feiden
  - Goldschmidt - Goldsmith (Box 20, Folder 153)
    Goldschmidt, Lucien Goldsmith, Yvonne B. Goldsmith, Christine M.
  - Goldwater - Gootzit (Box 20, Folder 154)
    Goldwater, Barry (Chair of American Institutions) Goldwater, Louise B. Goldwater, Robert Golik, Edwin Golikoff, Edwin Golton, Glenn Gombert, Hermann Gomez, Luis Duque Gomez-Sicro Goodall, Grace Goodman, James Goodman, Nena Goodnough, Robert Goodnow, Frank Goodson, Byron W. Goodstadt, George Goodyear, A. Conger Goodyear, William C. Gootzit, Paul L.
  - Gorbaci - Goyer (Box 20, Folder 155)
    Gorbaci, Nicolai Gordon, Albert F. Gordon, Antoinette Gordon, Elinor Gordon, Martin Gordon, Michael Gordon, Ruth Gorsline, Douglas Gottesman, Mrs. Ace Gottlieb, Grace Gottlieb, Henry Gotts, Herold Gotz, Janos Gouverneur, Hector H. Gouverneur, Simon Governor's Conference 1973, Republican Gowen, C. Allan Goya, Francisco de Goyer, Ruth C.
  - Grabow - Grazzini (Box 20, Folder 156)
    Grabow, Oliver M. Grace International Gracie, Charles R. & Sons Graham, Bob Graham, Douglas J. M. Graham, Daniel H. Graham Gallery Graham, Mrs. Graham, Robert C. Grand Central Art Gallery Granville, Philip (Lord's Gallery London) Graphic Arts Society Grasso, Mrs. Waltraud Graubert, Mrs. David Gray, Cleve Gray, Mrs. K. H. Gray, M. May Grayson, Kenneth Grazzini, Giampaolo
  - Greater - Gregory (Box 20, Folder 157)